The World's Smartest Resume Builder

* Builders
    
    Builders

    Making a resume is easy with the right tool. Our resume builder does the hard work for you.

    Short on time or simply don't like writing? Try our cover letter generator and make a cover letter fast.

    CVs are often longer than resumes. With our CV maker, you can create a CV in the same amount of time.
    
    Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)
    
* Resumes
    
    Resumes

    [Professional
    
    HR approved, organized, and stylish.](https://resumegenius.com/resume-templates/professional-templates)

    [Modern
    
    Contemporary templates perfect for your new job.](https://resumegenius.com/resume-templates/modern-templates)

    [Creative
    
    A little visual flair to highlight your creativity.](https://resumegenius.com/resume-templates/creative-templates)

    [Simple
    
    Basic templates that focus on your work experience.](https://resumegenius.com/resume-templates/basic-templates)

    Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)
    
* Cover Letters
    
    Cover Letters

    [Professional
    
    HR approved, organized, and stylish.](https://resumegenius.com/cover-letter-templates/professional-templates)

    [Modern
    
    Contemporary templates perfect for your new job.](https://resumegenius.com/cover-letter-templates/modern-templates)

    [Creative
    
    A little visual flair to highlight your creativity.](https://resumegenius.com/cover-letter-templates/creative-templates)

    [Simple
    
    Basic templates that focus on your work experience.](https://resumegenius.com/cover-letter-templates/basic-simple-templates)

    Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)
    
* CVs
    
    CVs

    [Business
    
    Professional CV templates for senior-level positions.](https://resumegenius.com/cv-template#business)

    [Graduate
    
    Templates for academics and scholars.](https://resumegenius.com/cv-template#graduate)

    [Research
    
    A format to showcase your research background.](https://resumegenius.com/cv-template#research)

    [Writer
    
    Perfect templates for published writers.](https://resumegenius.com/cv-template#writer)

    Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)
    
* Resources
    
    Resources

    * 

        Technical Assistance
    * 

        Resume FAQs
    * 

        Cover Letter FAQs
    * 

        CV FAQs

    Learn the ins and outs of writing a resume. From formatting to fonts, we cover every topic.

    Cover letter writing is a skill that will help you outshine other applicants. Our guides can teach you that skill.

    You're one step away from getting the job. Win over hiring managers with our expert interview tips.
    
    Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)

Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) and Saturdays and Sundays, 10AM – 6PM EDT [(866) 215-9048](tel:8662159048)

Privacy Policy
==============

**Last updated February 27, 2023**

Thank you for choosing ResumeGenius, owned by Sonaga Tech Limited, Hamilton, Zweigniederlassung Luzern (“Company”, “Service Provider”, “we”, “us” or “our”), to create your resume and cover letter. We are committed to protecting your information and your right to privacy. Your data controller is Sonaga Tech Limited, Hamilton, Zweigniederlassung Luzern If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at [support@resumegenius.com](mailto:support@resumegenius.com).

When you visit our website [https://resumegenius.com](https://resumegenius.com/) (the “Site”), and use any of the services, or you share with us with some personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy policy, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of the Site and our services.

This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our Site. It also applies to any service related to the Site, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy policy as the “Services“).

**Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.**

**Table of Contents**

1. [What information do we collect?](#what-information-do-we-collect)
2. [How do we use your information?](#how-do-we-use-your-information)
3. [Will your information be shared with anyone?](#will-your-information-be-shared-with-anyone)
4. [Do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?](#do-we-use-cookies-and-other-tracking-technologies)
5. [How do we handle your social account logins?](#how-do-we-handle-your-social-logins)
6. [How long do we keep your information?](#how-long-do-we-keep-your-information)
7. [How do we keep your information safe?](#how-do-we-keep-your-information-safe)
8. [Do we collect information from minors?](#do-we-collect-information-from-minors)
9. [What are your privacy rights?](#what-are-your-privacy-rights)
10. [Controls for do-not-track features](#controls-for-do-not-track-features)
11. [Do California residents have specific privacy rights?](#do-california-residents-have-specific-privacy-rights)
12. [Do we make updates to this policy?](#do-we-make-updates-to-this-policy)
13. [How can you contact us about this policy?](#how-can-you-contact-us)

1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
-----------------------------------

**Personal information you disclose to us**

We collect information that you provide to us when registering at the Site expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services, when participating in activities on the Services or otherwise contacting us. Please be informed that in some cases, providing some personal information will be required to use our service. Otherwise, we may not be in a position to render services. This relates in particular to your email address (if you decide to register the account) and information you provide while using our services.

The information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with the Site and the Services, the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect can include the following:

**Information Provided by You.** We collect data provided by You when using our services, that may be, for example, name, surname, email address, phone number, address, information you introduced to our tools (professional experience, information about your education, skills), but also collected from surveys, resumes and other job application data and other similar data.

**Credentials.** We collect passwords, password hints, and similar security information used for authentication and account access.

**Social Media Login Data.** We provide you with the option to register using social media account details, like your Facebook or another social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will collect the information described in the section called “[HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS](#how-do-we-handle-your-social-logins)” below.

All information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

We may collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Site and the Services. This information may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies. You can find out more about this in our [Cookie Policy](https://resumegenius.com/cookie-policy)

**Online Identifiers.** We collect devices, tools and protocols, such as IP (Internet Protocol) addresses, cookie identifiers, or others such as the ones used for analytics and marketing, device’s geolocation, and other similar data.

**Information collected from other sources**

We may collect information about you from third parties when you use your social media account to sign up with us. Examples of the data collected from this services are you email, first name, last name and login information from those third parties.

2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?
-----------------------------------

We use personal information collected via our Services for a variety of purposes as described below. We process your information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely for the reasons described next to each purpose listed below.

We use the information we collect or receive:

* **To facilitate account creation and login process.** If you choose to link your third-party social media account to your account with us (such as your Google or Facebook account), we may use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and log-in process for the performance of the contract. See the section below headed “ [HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS](#how-do-we-handle-your-social-logins)” for further information.
* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We may use the information you send to us for marketing purposes as this is our legitimate interest. You can opt-out of our marketing emails from us at any time (see the “ [WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS](#what-are-your-privacy-rights)” below). Marketing emails from our partners will only be sent to you if you grant your consent.
* **To provide you with our Services:** to respond to your questions and requests; (ii) provide customer service, (e.g., to fulfill product and service orders made by you, give you information about your account to resolve disputes, problems with your account/profile or the Site, administer a contest, sweepstakes or promotions. We may use your information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. (iii) request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
* **To post testimonials.** We post testimonials on our Services that may contain user information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we will obtain your consent to use your name and testimonial. If you wish to update, or delete your testimonial, please contact us at privacy@resumegenius.com and be sure to include your name, testimonial location, and contact information.
* **Deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may use your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness. This is our legitimate business interest. For more information, see our [Cookie Policy](https://resumegenius.com/cookie-policy).
* **Administer prize draws and competitions.** We may use your information to administer prize draws and competitions when you elect to participate in competitions.
* **Request Feedback.** We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
* **To protect our Services.** We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Services safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).
* **To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.** If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond. This is our legitimate interest.
* **For location-based services.** When you access our Site through your mobile device we may access your location to provide you location-based services and other personalized content. This is our legitimate interest.
* **For other Business Purposes.** We may use your information for other Business Purposes (this is our legitimate interest), such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Services, marketing and your experience. We may use and store this information in aggregated and anonymized form so that it is not associated with individual end users and does not include personal information.

3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?
------------------------------------------------

We may share data with:

* **Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Services, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Services over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. We may also share your information with third parties if the activity is understood to be illegal, fraudulent or posts a potential threat to security. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We have contracts in place with our data processors and have instructed them to hold your data securely and use it only for the purpose set out in the contract.If you are a EU resident, please note that we are cooperating with vendors all over the world. That is why your data may be transferred outside European Economic Area (“EEA”). We are making the best effort to ensure your data is safe. That is why transfer will only take place in accordance with the applicable regulations To obtain a copy of the relevant transfer mechanism or additional information on the transfers, please address these requests to legal@resumegenius.com
* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. This may only take place in accordance with applicable laws, for example when after the assessment of effectuated by the parties to the transaction, such legitimate interest is not overdriven by your interest or fundamental rights and freedoms
* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions

4\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?
------------------------------------------------------

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our [Cookie Policy](https://resumegenius.com/cookie-policy).

5\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL ACCOUNT LOGINS?
------------------------------------------------

Our Services offer you the ability to register and login using your third-party social media account details. Where you choose to do this, we may receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile Information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, email address, friends list, profile picture as well as other information you choose to make public.

We use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy policy or that are otherwise made clear to you on the Site. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third-party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy policy to understand how they collect, use and share your information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

6\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
-----------------------------------------

We will only keep your information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). When your data is processes based on our legitimate interest (for example, for data analysis, or to respond to your legal request) you can always object to such processing. If you object to the processing of your personal data we will discontinue such processing if the objection is well-founded by law.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

If data is processed based on your consent, we will process it until you withdraw your consent. If you wish to revoke your consent please [Contact us](https://resumegenius.com/contact).

7\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?
-----------------------------------------

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your information, transmission of information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the services within a secure environment. Our Data Protection Officer may be contacted by sending an email to [dpo@sonagatech.com](mailto:dpo@sonagatech.com).

8\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?
------------------------------------------

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18. If we learn that information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com).

9\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?
---------------------------------

Based on the laws of some countries, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to access, update, or delete your personal information, please submit a request by clicking [here](https://resumegenius.com/data-access/personal-data). You can also make your request by sending an email to [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com) or contacting one of our representatives through the phone number provided [here](#how-can-you-contact-us). We will respond to your request within the timeframe provided by law.

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please submit a request by clicking [here](https://resumegenius.com/data-access/personal-data), or send us an email to [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com) or use the [contact details](#how-can-you-contact-us) provided in Section 18, below. You also have a right afforded by Article 77 of GDPR to file a complaint with the competent data protection authority. This complaint may be filed where the data protection breach occurred, at your place of work or your residence.

Please know that some minimal information will be requested for identification purposes and as a safeguard to your privacy before providing access to your personal data. If you do not provide this information it will affect our ability to provide the information requested in a timely matter. GDPR provides us the right to refuse and/or charge a fee for requests that are found to be manifestly unfounded or excessive. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws. For purposes of this section your data controller is Sonaga Tech Limited, Hamilton, Zweigniederlassung Luzern.

We have appointed EDPO, Avenue Huart Hamoir 71 – 1030 Brussels, Belgium, as our EU representative for GDPR purposes. If you want to exercise your rights with respect to your personal data, you may do so by sending an email to [legal@sonagatech.com](mailto:legal@sonagatech.com)

We value privacy of our customers and strive to comply with all applicable privacy laws, including UK GDPR. All rights described in section 9 apply accordingly to UK residents. We have appointed EDPO UK, 8 Northumberland Avenue – W2CN 5BY London, UK, as our UK privacy representative. You may contact us via our representative and exercise your rights by sending an email to [legal@sonagatech.com](mailto:legal@sonagatech.com)

If we are relying on your consent to process your information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com)

**Account Information** 

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:

■  Log into your account settings and update your user account.

■  Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon receiving your request to terminate your account, we will proceed to deactivate it. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit [https://optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN). For further information, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://resumegenius.com/cookie-policy).

**Opting out of email marketing:** You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided below. You will then be removed from the marketing email list – however, we will still need to send you service-related emails that are necessary for the administration and use of your account. To otherwise opt-out, you may:

■  Note your preferences when you register an account with the site.

■  Access your account settings and update preferences.

■  Contact us using the contact information below.

10\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES
---------------------------------------

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy policy.

11\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?
----------------------------------------------------------

This section exclusively and only applies from users that are California residents in compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). “Personal information”, according to the CCPA is “information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.” The California Privacy Regulations Act (CPRA), which amends the CCPA, states that “Sell,” “selling,” “sale,” or “sold,” means selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a consumer’s personal information by the business to a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration. Because CPRA has broaden the definition of selling, in some cases when we share your data it may be considered a sell. When you visit our page, create an account, subscribe, or use our services we may drop cookies or web beacons and share personal information with our service providers or third parties, as part of providing our services. You will find more details about the third parties we share information with and the purpose in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, we have included an option in our main page for you to opt-out of the selling or sharing of your personal information. In case you opt-out we will honor that request for at least 12 months. There is an identification process as part of the request, so we ask you to please complete the form with accurate information. We will also honor Do not Sell or Share my Information requests from Nevada residents, in compliance with privacy regulations. In case you want to complete your request through an authorized agent the representative will need to provide the necessary information to validate their appointment. You can also send a Do Not Sell or Share my personal Information request by email to [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com)

There are certain requirements we must meet if any financial incentives are offered to California residents in connection with our handling of their personal information (we improve our offering when the difference in pricing, rates or quality of goods is reasonably related to the value of the California resident’s personal information).

If you are a California resident, subject to some exceptions, you have the following rights:

1. **The right to request deletion of personal information** that we have collected about you.
2. **The right to request a copy of the specific pieces of personal information** that we have collected about you in the last 12 months.
3. **The right to request that we disclose certain information how we have handled your personal information in the prior 12 months** which include the categories of personal information collected and sources of personal information, the business purposes for collecting and selling personal information, the categories of third parties with whom we have shared your personal information, the categories of personal information that we have disclosed with a third party for a business purpose, the categories of personal information collected and the categories of third parties to whom your personal information has been sold and the specific categories of personal information sold to each category of third parties.

We may collect and share for a business purpose the following personal information from California residents:

1. name, contact information and identifiers – real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers.
2. customer records – electronic customer records containing personal information, such as name, signature, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, education, employment, employment history.
3. protected classifications – characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law such as race, color, sex, age, religion, national origin, disability, citizenship status, and genetic information.
4. purchase history and tendencies – commercial information including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
5. usage data – internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a California consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement.
6. geolocation data – precise geographic location information about a particular individual or device.
7. employment history – professional or employment-related information.
8. education information – information about education history or background.
9. AudioVisual – audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.
10. Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a California consumer reflecting the California consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.

The categories above do not address our handling of personal information that is subject to an exemption under Section 1798.145(c) – (f) of the CCPA.

You may submit a deletion, copy and right to know request online by emailing us at [privacy@resumegenius.com](mailto:privacy@resumegenius.com) or contacting us at the toll-free number in the contact us section below. CCPA prohibit business any type of discrimination against California residents that exercise their CCPA rights.

12\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?
---------------------------------------

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

13\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?
----------------------------------------------

If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may contact us by calling to (866) 215-9048 (available Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) EDT), by sending an email to privacy@resumegenius.com, or by post to Sonaga Tech Limited, Hamilton, Zweigniederlassung Luzern, Hertensteinstrasse 51, 6004 Luzern, Switzerland.

Resumes

Cover Letters

CVs

Policies

Additional Resources

Support

Member of

[

](https://parwcc.com/)[

](https://parwcc.com/page/CPRW_new)

© 2024, Sonaga Tech Limited. All rights reserved

ResumeGenius.com is owned and operated by Sonaga Tech Limited, Hamilton, Zweigniederlassung Luzern with offices in Luzern Switzerland.

Close

Thanks for downloading our free template!

Would you leave us a review?
----------------------------

We hope we’ve helped you on your path to career success. If you have time, a quick review would really make our day (it'll only take 15 seconds). Thanks again, and good luck!

  4.5 / 5 Based on [38777 reviews](https://www.trustpilot.com/review/resumegenius.com) powered by  

Scroll to top
